<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>mutualaid.info</title>
    <link>https://mutualaid.info/</link>
    <description>Recent content on mutualaid.info</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mutualaid.info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using OpenBSD&#39;s in-kernel WireGuard support to route some local hosts over a VPN</title>
      <link>https://mutualaid.info/posts/wireguard-openbsd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mutualaid.info/posts/wireguard-openbsd/</guid>
      <description>This post is a follow-up to Routing some local hosts over a WireGuard VPN on an OpenBSD router, which detailed how to use the userland implementation of WireGaurd, wireguard-go, on OpenBSD to route a specific local host or subnet over a WireGuard VPN. I&amp;rsquo;ve finally upgraded to OpenBSD 6.8, so this post will cover how to use the new in-kernel WireGuard support from the wg(4) driver to accomplish the same goal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Routing some local hosts over a WireGuard VPN on an OpenBSD router</title>
      <link>https://mutualaid.info/posts/wireguard-go-openbsd/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mutualaid.info/posts/wireguard-go-openbsd/</guid>
      <description>WireGuard kernel support on OpenBSD is coming (hopefully) soon! It&amp;rsquo;s not in the -current branch or snapshots quite yet. The repository where it&amp;rsquo;s being worked on is here and patches have been submitted by the developers to the tech@ mailing list. Once kernel support is in the -current branch of OpenBSD, I&amp;rsquo;ll try to publish an updated post using the kernel support instead of wireguard-go.
 I was inspired to write this by a friend who wanted to automatically tunnel traffic from specific devices on their local network over a WireGuard VPN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flashing USBaspLoader and QMK to an ATmega328P</title>
      <link>https://mutualaid.info/posts/usbasploader-qmk-atmega328p/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mutualaid.info/posts/usbasploader-qmk-atmega328p/</guid>
      <description>This is a super high level (and probably incomplete in some places) guide and list of resources related to using a Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s GPIO pins to flash USBaspLoader onto an ATmega328P microcontroller unit (MCU) and flashing QMK onto it over USB. I wrote it up after learning a bit about circuit design and MCU programming, and I hope it&amp;rsquo;s helpful as a resource to others.
Software prerequisites You need to have avrdude and avr-gcc installed on a Raspberry Pi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://mutualaid.info/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mutualaid.info/contact/</guid>
      <description>email</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
